This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever!
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it!
We are whole from the horizon
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that I'd want to
take you to, Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know,
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated, It
crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together I'm
telling you in our path I trust that it
will lead us To another sea untarded
Cause now we are home On the horizon,
out on the edge of the world
There is a place that I
want to take you to Let's
head for it then But after
the way we already know
We promised it long ago
Jinbei came here to help?
Uh-huh, really surprised me too That's
a relief So Nami's in good hands then
One problem I don't know how we'll
be able to meet up with them again,
but once they find out
that you're coming back,
they'll be real happy.
Now we're through.
I'm sorry.
Sorry we ever came here.
I'm too ashamed to ever
face Nami after this.
Things will work out.
Nami and the rest of our friends
have been pretty worried about you.
I don't know.
I dragged everyone through hell and back.
Look.
It's clearing up.
It's right here, Ria!
Good job!
Do you think he'll be able to hear us
through this tiny shard? I think so.
When I spoke to you through the mirror
before, the whole thing cracked apart.
But the pieces should
still be on that tree.
It broke!
Let's try.
If even a single shard that connects to
this mirror is still there, we're good.
Hey! Luffy! Hey! Luffy!
Hey!
Are you there?
On the tree?
That chopper?
It's got to be.
Hello!
It's me if you hear me!
Over here, Chopper!
It's Luffy!
Hey!
I'll keep yelling if
you follow my voice, OK?
Aha!
Hey, Chopper!
Can't believe you guys found me!
Well, Nami was right!
Why is Chopper's voice
coming from a mirror?
It's kind of a long story, but they're
all in another dimension right now.
How's that possible?
Hey, Chopper, you guys good?
Yeah, Luffy! We're fine!
Sounds like you are, too!
Luffy!
Was that Sanji?
Uh-huh.
He's here with me.
Tell Sanji that we're all glad he's safe.
So how are ya?
I'm happy to report everyone has been
rescued and is currently safe in the mirror.
For now.
And guess what?
Brooke even scored us a
copy of Big Mom's poneglyph.
That's amazing.
I knew you'd do it. Good job.
You big mushy jerk face.
You can't butter us up like that.
Yeah, doofus.
WHAT!?
You silly little goose!
Anyway, while it's great you Karoo
found Sanji, I hope things are settled?
Being honest, not exactly!
So here's the deal:
we're crashing big mom's tea party
and busting up Sanji's wedding!
Plus we're gonna save his family too
after that he's coming home for good.
Big Mom, huh?
Uh, yeah.
No way.
She's much too strong for us.
I would never risk Nami's, I mean,
everybody's life for my own problems.
Okay?
Let's do it!
It's fine, whatever!
I heard that you and Lumi
got into a huge fight!
I was so worried, you look!
I'm so happy! You too! You too!
You're so fool!
So basically, we help out Sanji.
And he comes back okay.
Hey, was that Nami?
Oh, by the way, don't think
I'll let you off easy.
For You're freaking me
out like that, Sanji.
I'll never forgive you.
Nami!
Let's forget about that for now.
We're short on time, we gotta focus.
The tea party will be starting soon,
and I'll have the rest
of my life to resent you.
Was that a proposal?
Yes, Nami! Hey!
Nice, Sanji.
You're back to normal, that's great.
Very well, Luffy.
I believe we know what to do.
Glad you're in.
Oh, and I should mention,
Sanji's sister saved me.
So I want to help her, too.
Yes, I'm in agreement.
However, this won't be easy.
Even though we're not aiming
to defeat Big Mom herself,
she enjoys those tea parties more
than anything else in the world.
By crashing it,
we'll no doubt be provoking the wrath
of one of the Emperors of the Sea.
And she's not the only concern.
I'm sure you've had a run-in with
a couple of her ministers already.
But that's only scratching the
surface of the Big Mom Pirates.
There will be even more fearsome enemies
that will be in attendance
at that ceremony.
Not to mention,
underground moguls and other seedy
characters are also on the guest list.
The opposition will be meager but mighty.
The ten of us that are here.
Not us!
We refuse to help you!
Don't count us!
Your team's only got eight!
I hope your dumb plan gets you killed!
Luffy.
I have already informed
everyone that's gathered here.
But it's important that I share
this tidbit with you as well.
You're familiar with the
man Capone, Buggy, correct?
He's the guy who took Soji.
As a fellow member of the worst
generation, his reputation rivals Jerome.
He and his crewmates hail from the West
Blue and control the criminal underworld.
In fact, Mafia's run
rampant where he's from.
There's five families of the West,
and at the head of one of those
criminal organizations is Gang Buggy.
The name Gang traces back to his younger
days when he was a notorious hitman.
He killed people?
According to the rumors, as a young
lad, he was a sick individual.
He took great pleasure
in maiming the helpless
and watching the light
fade from their very eyes.
This guy sounds like he's really awful.
That same warp skill set is what
allowed him to thrive in crime.
How is the flavor sir?
It's not quite bitter enough for my taste!
Might I recommend the house special?
No boss.
You two-timed bastard!
How's that buddy bitter enough for you?
Even as a young mobster, he sought out the
most powerful bosses in the underworld.
After establishing his own family,
he killed any rival leader
he could, and no one else.
Benji?
Stick him up, sunshine.
Are you going rogue?
You're outmanned, my friend. Benji!
However, he never showed interest in
his enemy's position or territory.
He only take their valuables.
Chaos would always follow
his assassinations,
and he took great pleasure in watching
the different factions eat themselves
alive in bloody power struggles that man
truly is a tasteless fellow it's as they
say though sow the wind reap the whirlwind
he soon became a target of the many
hungry for a taste of sweet vengeance
nevertheless neji
reveled in that very
fact he built himself a powerful fortress
and fought them all off while mocking
his rival's efforts once he grew tired
with life on land he set out to sea and
repeated the same pattern what happened
here who did this to the captain damn it
he then became well known for taking out
the leaders of well-known pirate crews
needless to say that much notoriety
comes with some downsides as well
he now needed a safe haven from
his enemies so allying himself
with an emperor of the sea seemed
like the best course of action
big mom respected his finely honed
caution and defensive capabilities
So for the upcoming tea party,
he was granted the honorary
title of Rook and has
been entrusted with full
authority over security.
Yeah, okay, but why are you bringing
all this junk up now, Jinbei?
If the security guards are on our side,
then there will be nothing
that can stand in our way.
Huh?
What are you getting at?
The main event of the tea party
will be the wedding ceremony.
It is at this time that we think Big Mom
intends to take out the
entire Vinsmoke family
in order to seize control
of Jerma's assets.
But Veggie is planning to
take Big Mom's head himself.
What?
Are you for real?
We got conspiracies everywhere.
There's more.
Peckhams fell into Veggie's hands
after guiding you to this island.
And so he knows about
the assassination, too.
Buggy offered him a deal if he
cooperated with their proposal.
Did he agree?
I wondered about him.
Peckhams was too loyal to accept.
Buggy shot him into shark-infested
waters in order to silence him.
Aaaaaaahhhhhh!
Luckily, some of my companions witnessed
that and saved him in the nick of time.
He is currently recuperating.
That's a relief!
So he's okay?
Oh, that poor guy.
He's been through a lot of crap.
That's dirty!
Damn that veggie!
I'll make him pay!
Luffy, I have yet to make my main point.
Listen well.
After we learned of the assassination
plot from Peckhams, we made a plan.
I tried to anticipate how
you would handle this.
I knew one thing for certain, though.
Once you were wise to the scheme, you'd
want to rescue Sanji and his family.
i have sympathy for
peckham's but under these
circumstances can we really afford to make
an enemy of benji the
tea party starts at
10 in the morning roughly
five hours from now
that grants the 10 of us very
little time to craft up a plan
stop including us in your damn
number You ignorant morons!
We are so good at telling you all!
You must consider this.
Benji not only runs security, but has
fully prepared for tomorrow's operation.
Therefore, to succeed, I
propose we team up with him.
What?
Jinbei, I think you're right on.
Come on, seriously, Luffy?
You're agreeing to this plan?
That's the spirit I knew you would be!
Luffy, listen, this may be a bad idea!
You heard his backstory.
Veggie is a Newgate crook.
I don't know. Can't hurt.
It'll be worth a try.
Hey, think it over.
I've already made the arrangements.
When would you like to speak with it?
Now, let's go!
And don't worry you may
refuse if something feels
off our goal is slightly
different from theirs.
Anyway luffy sanji Buggy and
his men are set up in the
northwest part of the island the
eight of us will head directly
there from within this
dimension we'll see you shortly
you're counting us again aren't
you great meet you there?
Did you snuff out bobbin uh-huh i sure did
he was tailing blackleg
you can't threaten Germa
not on my watch you're
sure these guys won't
get cold feet more than
that you trust them?
Jinbei ain't no grifter
and he ain't no funny man.
Aside from sharing a common
interest with his pals
we don't want to make any new enemies.
if we plan on throwing lead at big mom
now the rest of this ride's on Straw Hat
if he tries anything funny
we'll pop him too.
To be
continued...
As all your tears flow once more.
And in the song of pain!
Brings forth more fear.
And so, since life is sad?
Let dessert be sweet.
A cake, oh, so sweet!
That it can't be made.
Let's share, let's share.
Love be delight.
Please don't, Peckhams.
You need your rest.
Get out.
Can you at least tell me that Jinbei went
to warn Mama about that backstabbing Page?
He can't get away with this.
Most certainly.
Don't worry.
I'd wager that by now, Big Mom must be
beating him within an inch of his life.
Get out.
A wager isn't good enough for me.
We're wasting time.
I'll do it myself.
Easy now.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Just focus on regaining
your strength. Relax.
But, Braylene, I'm worried.
I need to be sure that the
information will reach Mama.
Get out.
Peckhams, it's fine.
Believe in Jinbei.
You can't win a fight like this.
What if they do this again?
You will surely be killed.
I, too, forbid you from leaving.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
Agreed.
You need your R &R.
Listen to him!
Listen to her!
Dad, come on up, man.
We love you, Dad.
What's going on?
I'm getting kind of skeptical here.
Something's odd.
I noticed.
A lot of night activity.
Also, I swear, I saw you
guys moving around luggage.
Look, I do appreciate that you saved
my life at all, but I gotta go.
No, no, no.
We can't allow that.
What do you mean, allow?
Get out!
What could you be hiding from me?
We made it.
That's his base.
so this veggie what's he like you heard
what jimbae said yellow-bellied rat
let's be careful we've never dealt
with a cutthroat mafia boss before
Oh, my hero Lili, Vinsmoke
Sanji of Germa, welcome back.
Now this is a treat, I'm delighted that
you have made it. Oh boy, it's him.
Hey, you bitchy, let's gather your crew.
Let's not rush things, shall we?
You could at least give me a hello Lili.
Screw your Lelos!
Oh, there you guys are!
Soji!
You made me so worried, you bastard!
Sorry, my bad. Huh?
You look, uh, comfortable?
Oh, totally!
You two, come take a bath!
No!
We don't have time!
How are you so relaxed?
You don't even like baths!
I'm afraid you have no say in the matter.
Go scrub up, then we'll talk a little.
You're forcing us to bathe?
Clearly, Lili.
The Godfather won't meet
with an unclean guest.
We're not dirty.
What?
Lola was turned into a warthog zombie?
There's more.
She chased down a guy
because she was lovesick.
Boy, does that sound like her.
I don't know what I would
have done without Lola.
She saved me back then, and she saved
me now with that tree monster, too.
So you say, but it sounds to me
like you saved Lola just as much.
I appreciate it.
Just look at me, cry and
see the joy. Excuse me.
We've been close ever
since we were little kids.
We're twins, you know.
Zombies?
Dead people walking around again?
The sea's such a wonderland.
So then, did Moa turn back
into a human? She did.
I'm sure she's living her
best life as a pirate.
I always think of her.
I hope she found love.
From what I remember, Big
Mom was upset with her.
For running away from a marriage?
That's right!
It was a big scandal.
Yeah?
All the world's giants despise Mama?
For something that happened before.
They all hate her?
Sounds serious.
Yeah, so even though there's a
diverse population. In Totoland.
There are no giants here. Nope.
Giants are real.
One day,
a man showed up,
claiming it was love at first sight
and had interest in marrying Lola.
Turns out he was Loki, the prince of Elbaf,
the giant's country. A prince? No way!
Mama was practically brought to tears.
If Lola became the princess of Elbaf,
her long-standing feud with
the giants would be resolved.
She also had her eyes set
on their massive army,
which is said to be amongst
the world's strongest.
I gotcha.
So that's why she ran away, huh?
After that, things got messy.
Mama even tried to pass me off as Lola.
Naturally, the prince noticed right away.
This made things even worse.
Mama got desperate.
She abandoned the entire idea of having
genuine giants here in Toto Land.
Instead, she started investing in
research to gigantify normal people.
Her rage towards Lola had grown even stronger,
and then Mama branded her a criminal.
So, if she comes back, she'll be killed.
And considering I look just like her,
Mama can't stand the sight of me anymore.
I'm sick of your face.
It disgusts me to look at you.
When i was around she took it out
on me she beat and abused me for
years that Woman is a monster she's
no mother to me forcing her own
daughter to fear for her life it's
terrible
but
Lola
is a free spirit
the thought that mama would want a
killer would never even cross a mind.
She's too pure-hearted.
It all makes sense now.
We've both had it bad.
Well, That's why when Veggie
said that he would murder Mama,
I didn't feel anything inside.
Am I a bad person?
I know. It's wrong.
Goodness!
What a wonderful path!
So that's what heaven is like.
Don't you tempt
It feels like we wrapped up a big fight,
but it's just starting. Don't get comfy.
Luffy? Luffy?
Look what I found! Come quickly!
I found milk!
Hey, stop!
At least ask before you
guys look in our fridge.
That's just what I needed.
Here, look, my tooth cracked. Me too.
Rather, my whole face cracked.
Thanks.
We needed this.
How the hell is that even possible?
I won't forgive you, Siobhan.
Unbelievable.
Really?
You're really gonna help the enemy?
You're a traitor.
It got over please you know it those guys
don't stand a chance mama will be livid.
Listen Barrel you know what she's
done to me that woman's evil.
Lola's in danger too veggie and pez
are my family no one else matters.
Oh it's okay sweetie.
Great.
That should be everybody.
Your keisters are so clean you
could eat off of them, right?
They say clothes make the man.
Well, I won't humor no mooks who
don't care about their appearance.
okay there's three and a half hours to go
let's decide are we
doing this or no deal
You two just can't help
yourselves, can you?
Huh?
You're not for us to eat? Try one.
You guys are nothing
but a liability to me.
Commit me otherwise.
The tidiest solution for this would
be to murder you all on the spot.
Think it over.
If I die, you're throwing away
your one chance to kill Big Mom.
There'll be no wedding.
Plus, if I'm not back there at
least two hours before the wedding,
they'll come snooping.
Point taken.
I can figure out a
workaround for that, though.
How's about I off your pals?
I don't have time for Intimidation Gage!
Luffy, what's your intuition
telling you about this man?
Trustworthy?
Why is Caesar here?
It's Caesar! Where? Where?
Come on, man.
He's right there.
How could you not notice?
This research is never
going to lead us anywhere.
I'm giving up now before I go crazy.
Do your worst, Big Mom.
You think I'm afraid of you?
Seize a clown, I presume?
I was taking five. Don't worry.
Tell Big Mom I'm working my ass off.
Not necessary.
What?
See, I was put in charge
of watching over you.
All I had to do was ask somebody.
I do as I please now
that I'm a trusted rook.
That's mine, Curse you!
I can bust you out of here, but I'm
gonna need you to scratch my back.
You numbskull!
Just who in the hell do you
think you're talking to anyway?
Do you realize I'm capable
of destroying the world?
I'm a genius, you know!
No!
Yeah, I'm aware.
That's why I'm here.
Bastards!
First Big Mom and now Veggie.
How dare they put me to
work like I'm some dog?
Working on your task still, Lili? Clearly.
Just who do you take me for, huh?
Besides, this project's
more my cup of tea anyway.
Every minute, I inch closer to
completing my greatest work of art.
Good to know, Lili.
The Straw Hats are on their way
and should be arriving shortly.
They're coming here!
I hope to never see those losers again.
When they're around, anything
that can go wrong will!
The Godfather wanted me to tell you you
will be attending the meeting too, Lili.
Oh, don't be late.
This is a fine mess.
I have no choice.
Oh, Caesar.
I'm, uh, Veggie's older half-brother.
The name's Gangster
Gastino, you little punk.
He's not even trying to hide it at all.
That name is so fake.
Really, Caesar?
His laugh, it's still the same.
My mistake. Different
guy. Sorry about that.
You were great, Luffy.
That's obviously Caesar. You liar!
I knew it had to be you.
What are you doing here anyway?
Do you think this is my choice?
Use your head, dummy.
Please don't tell me you people
forgot where you last left me.
My only ticket out of a certain death
was to become this bozo's personal slave.
He's holding my heart, you know.
You better tell Trafalgar Law that
I'm gonna gut him when I see him.
Then I'm coming for you
after. All right, enough.
Can it, you two?
You're wasting my precious time.
Lay it on me.
We gonna play nice?
Oh, are we done?
Let me punch you for shooting
Peckums first, then we can talk!
Uh, Lili?
Are you ready?
There's no time for this!
Put your fist down right now.
This isn't helping the situation.
But this jerk shot my buddy.
How dare you speak to the
Godfather like that. Got it.
Lower your barrel, Fall.
Would you stop? It's okay. Let him go.
I kicked them out already.
Don't tell me what to do.
Give me a break.
Oh
Then that one fact alone makes
us allies we may not share
ideals or lifestyles but we
all have a common enemy here?
Settle your differences at a later time!
Everyone's cooperation will be
necessary for gaining the upper hand.
What's your plan?
I've got every last detail worked out.
Let's get it over with.
Then I'll be done with you fools for good.